thefirstgroup.com 2019-12-12

# Read TFG's Privacy Policy | The First Group

The First Group is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you a powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to The First Group's family of websites and those of its affiliates and governs data collection and usage. By using The First Group website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

##### COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The First Group collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. The First Group also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your post code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by The First Group. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by The First Group for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of The First Group website.

The First Group encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from The First Group so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. The First Group is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of The First Group and The First Group family of websites.

##### GENERAL USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The First Group collects and uses your personal information to operate The First Group website and deliver the services you have requested. The First Group also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The First Group and its affiliates. By completing and sending an enquiry form through this website or other The First Group websites, you are providing explicit permission to be contacted by email, sms or telephone about The First Group property investment offerings and promotions and agreeing to our having possession of and retaining any information that you provide to us. Upon initial contact, you will always be given an opportunity to opt-out of future communications. You may also opt-out using the unsubscribe function in the email you receive from us. The First Group may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

The First Group does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. The First Group may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, The First Group may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The First Group, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The First Group does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

The First Group keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within The First Group family's websites, in order to determine which First Group products and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customised content and advertising to customers and potential customers of The First Group whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

The First Group websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The First Group or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The First Group; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The First Group website, or the public.

##### European Union Users

Legal basis under EU General Data Protection Regulation for processing personal information of EU residents (“Personal Information”).

Where you have consented to data processing, your consent provides the legal basis to process your Personal Information. You have the right to withdraw consent at any time.

We may also process your Personal Information on the basis of contractual necessity to perform a contract we have with you. For example, when we process your credit card details when you provide them to make a payment.

We may also process your Personal Information on the basis of our legitimate interests, including in providing and improving our services. For example, The First Group has a legitimate interest in understanding your website visit history so we can assess your interests and provide a better experience. We also have a legitimate interest in providing and developing interesting features to provide to our users.

Where we rely on legitimate interests to process your Personal Information, you have the right to object to such processing (meaning that you can ask us to stop). You can contact us, using the details below, to object to other forms of processing.

##### USE OF COOKIES

The First Group websites use cookies (small files stored on your browser), web beacons, pixels and device identifiers (collectively also known as “cookies”) to help us personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize The First Group pages, or register with The First Group or its family of websites or services, a cookie helps The First Group to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same The First Group website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use The First Group features that you customised.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of The First Group services or its websites that you visit.

(a) third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from our website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads,

(b) Users can opt-out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting anytime by going to [www.aboutads.info/choice](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/) and exercise their choice.

##### Security of your Personal Information

The First Group secures your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. The First Group secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

##### RETENTION

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Notice unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

##### REFERRAL PROGRAMS

Should you engage in our referral program to tell an individual about The First Group, we will ask you for their name, email address and phone number. You must ensure you have the person’s permission to do so for the purposes detailed in this Privacy Notice. We will contact them by email and/or phone number to discuss The First Group’s product offering. The First Group stores this information for the sole purpose of following up on the contact request and tracking the success of our referral program. Referred individuals may contact us at info@thefirstgroup.com  to request that their information be deleted from our database.

##### MINORS

The First Group does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, do not enter information on this website or engage our services. If you believe a child of yours under the age of 18 has entered personal information please contact us to have the data removed.

##### Changes to this Statement

The First Group will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The First Group encourages you to periodically review this Statement to remain informed as to how The First Group is protecting and using your information.

##### Contact Information 

The First Group welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The First Group has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The First Group at info@thefirstgroup.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
